Hello everyone and welcome to
English Pod, my name is Marco.
My name is Catherine and as you've noticed
on our website we have a number of lessons
about giving a presentation
in English so this
is one of those lessons today we're
talking about avoiding questions.
That's right today in
part five or presentation
series we're going to
try and handle some
questions or avoid
questions as Catherine said.
So why don't we jump into
the dialogue let's see what
Mr. Ford is talking about
now and we'll be back in a bit.
Now as we've already discussed there's a
huge untapped market out there both in Asia
and other developing markets and in the
more mature markets for us to push into.
Now of course this
represents an enormous
challenge with enormous
rewards for the winners
but for any new product we need a great
marketing message and marketing campaign.
It needs to be directed and
focused at our target consumer
and needs to be pitched
at exactly the right level.
The question we
must first address is of
course who is our target
consumer and secondly
what do they expect from the
next generation alpha laptop?
Let's first of all tackle
the first question.
Our target consumer
for the X420 is the
middle class white collar worker
within above average income.
However as we
mentioned before the total
number of computer
owners is expanding rapidly
and we need to broaden
our audience for this product.
For example the X420 is also
ideally suited to a younger student
sector who might use laptops
both for studying and gaming.
There's no doubt that.
Mr. Ford if I could just
interrupt a moment you
say that the computer
is suitable for students
but you don't think the price of the
X420 is just too much for most students?
Well that's a fair point.
If you don't mind
I'd like to tackle your
question a little bit
later in the Q&A section.
Is that okay?
Yes sure.
Okay so as I was saying we have an
exciting campaign planned for the X420.
Firstly we'll have a
nationwide television
campaign as well as advertising on radio
and also in mini computer publications.
We also intend to.
I'm sorry to stop you
Mr. Ford but do you
really think that a television
campaign is cost effective?
I mean how much is that going to cost?
Well I don't have the figures
to hand but I'd be happy
to discuss those figures with
you after the presentation.
Okay let me just go
on and talk a little more
about the exciting
campaign we have in store.
Alright we're back and now we can
get started with language takeaway.
Language takeaway.
Okay so Marco a lot of
the conversation today
was about markets
and a target consumer.
So perhaps we should
start talking a little
bit about who Mr. Ford thinks
this company's consumers are.
That's right he
mentioned that the alpha
laptop could also be
aimed at the middle class.
We have different
classes in society and
especially in America
where we talk about people
who are low income they don't make very
much money or people who make a lot of money
they're rich, they're
on top but high class.
Yeah high class but in
the middle we have the
middle class and this
is just average people
they make money they have a car
they're not rich but they're not poor.
Okay so they're in the middle.
So this is the middle
class the computer is
aimed at the middle
class market but he said
that it's middle class
white collar worker.
Okay so I know this
this phrase exists in many
other languages but
a white collar worker in
English means refers to the
color of the shirt that you wear.
So white collar workers
usually work in offices.
So because they're usually wearing suits.
That's right they have
to wear nice clothes like
suits and button down
shirts but we sometimes
also talk about blue collar
workers who are these guys.
Blue collar workers are usually are usually
people that are in trades like for example
in mechanic or a plumber because usually
you see them wearing those blue shirts.
Yeah uniforms they
usually people who work
with their hands or who are
not likely to work in the big office.
So usually maybe these people are not
middle class maybe they are lower class.
They can be both in
America right now I think
you can make quite a bit of money if
you're a plumber or a construction worker.
That's right but he
also mentioned middle
class white collar worker
within above average income.
Okay so an income is the amount
of money that a person earns.
Usually in a year so we say $30,000 a year.
That's your annual income.
That's right so when we talk about something
that's average that means it's normal.
But in this case we're
not talking about
something that's average
what we're talking about.
It's above average.
Above average so if
the average income of a
person in America is
$36,000 a year on above
average income is $70,000
a year or $65,000 a year.
But for the middle class
maybe that's different.
So in the middle class an average
annual income is $70,000 and
above average income in the
middle class is $120,000 a year.
So the phrase there
above average you're
just referring to something
that's more than the normal.
That's right so in this case
more than the normal income
for a middle class worker
you can also say below average.
So a below average income is
lower than most people earn.
Okay very good and
well continuing on talking
about markets and the demographics
who we're selling the computer to.
We also talked about our target consumer.
Oh this is something
that you often hear in
meetings at work or in
marketing departments.
A target is something you aim for.
It's something you want to hit or achieve.
And so a target consumer is the
buyer is a customer that you aim to have.
So maybe you have
some customers that their
students and you have some
customers they're very old.
But your target consumer
are the people that
you really want to reach out to in this
case the middle class white collar worker.
That's right.
So in the case of our
dialogue our target
consumer is a middle class
white collar worker for example.
Okay so a lot of marketing stuff here
talking about the computer and what Mr.
Ford was saying.
Let's take a pause.
Let's listen to the dialogue
again and boy back
with some phrases on
how to defer questions.
Now as we've already discussed there's a
huge untapped market out there both in Asia
and other developing markets and in the
more mature markets for us to push into.
Now of course this
represents an enormous
challenge with enormous
rewards for the winners.
But for any new product we need a great
marketing message and marketing campaign.
It needs to be directed and
focused at our target consumer
and needs to be pitched
at exactly the right level.
The question we
must first address is of
course who is our target
consumer and secondly
what do they expect from the
next generation alpha laptop.
Let's first of all tackle
the first question.
Our target consumer
for the X420 is the middle
class white collar worker
within above average income.
However as we
mentioned before the total
number of computer
owners is expanding rapidly
and we need to broaden
our audience for this product.
For example the X420 is also
ideally suited to a younger student
sector who might use laptops
both for studying and gaming.
There's no doubt that.
Mr.
Ford if I could just interrupt a moment.
You say that the
computer is suitable for
students but you
don't think the price of
the X420 is just too
much for most students.
Well that's a fair point.
If you don't mind
I'd like to tackle your
question a little bit
later in the Q&A section.
Is that okay?
Yes sure.
Okay so as I was saying we have an
exciting campaign planned for the X420.
Firstly we'll have a
nationwide television
campaign as well as advertising on radio
and also in mini computer publications.
We also intend to.
I'm sorry to stop you
Mr. Ford but do you really
think that a television
campaign is cost effective?
I mean how much is that going to cost?
Well I don't have the figures to hand.
But I'd be happy to discuss those
figures with you after the presentation.
Okay let me just go
on and talk a little more
about the exciting
campaign we have in store.
Alright we're back so
now let's take a look
at those phrases that we
mentioned on Fluency Builder.
Fluency Builder.
So Marco there was a
phrase that I heard twice
in today's dialogue that I
think we should talk about.
The verb is to tackle. So we
heard to tackle a question.
Right so when Mr. Ford
says I'll tackle that
question a little bit
later on. He's talking
about I'll answer the question or
I'll talk about that question later on.
Right but in this
word to tackle there's
something kind of physical
about it because you
know in football we
say that when someone
tries to hit the ball from
someone else it's a slide tackle.
Right and so to tackle a question
means to really to really jump into
it and try and solve it
and it's you know maybe
not an easy question. So
I'm going to tackle that later.
I'm going to tackle a challenge.
Okay it's more than
just to solve a problem
or to answer questions. So maybe you can
also tackle a project, a difficult project.
That's right so you know what I'm going
to give us two weeks to tackle this project
because it's a
very difficult one.
Alright very good and well
actually when he was getting
some questions from the
audience members specifically
because he was kind
of being interrupted.
He was very polite
about it and to kind of
defer the question he
said you know what that's
a fair point but I'll tackle
that question later on.
Okay and so this is a really great phrase
if you want to if you want to flatter
someone make them
feel good before you tell
them that you're not
going to answer their
question or maybe you
disagree with someone.
So I could say you know
Marco chocolate cake
is the only cake in
the entire world that
people should eat. Okay
and I could say something
like that's a fair point
but in my opinion
vanilla cake is better. Alright so see what
Marco did he made me feel good he said you
know fair point that's
a good idea but I
disagree or but you
know in this in the case
of the today's dialogue
but we'll talk about that later.
Right and actually he did another
smart thing or in the way that he used his
language skills here
when he was interrupted
again he said hey you
know what I'd be happy
to answer your
questions at a later time
or in the Q&A session. Okay
so this phrase I'd be happy to.
I'd be happy to talk about that
at a later time but right now I'm trying
to explain something else. Exactly so these
are two really really
key phrases for trying
to in a nice way change
the topic or change
the conversation. So
yeah I guess you can say
yeah I'd be happy to
talk about that later
on or I'll tackle that question in a little
bit or that's a fair point but we'll talk
about it later on.
Okay so a lot of great
language there why
don't we take a last listen
to our dialogue and review
everything we've just learned.
Now as we've already discussed
there's a huge untapped market out there
both in Asia in other
developing markets and
in the more mature
markets for us to push into.
Now of course this represents an enormous
challenge with enormous rewards for the
winners but for any new
product we need a great
marketing message
and marketing campaign.
It needs to be directed
and focused at our target
consumer and needs to be pitched at exactly
the right level. The question we must
first address is of
course who is our target
consumer and secondly what do they expect
from the next generation alpha laptop.
Let's first of all tackle
the first question.
Our target consumer
for the X420 is the
middle class white collar worker
within above average income.
However as we mentioned before
the total number of computer owners is
expanding rapidly and
we need to broaden our
audience for this product. For example
the X420 is also ideally suited to younger
students sector who
might use laptops both for
studying and gaming.
There's no doubt that.
Mr. Ford if I could just
interrupt a moment.
You say that the
computer is suitable for
students but you don't
think the price of the
X420 is just too much for most students.
Well that's a fair point. If you don't mind
I'd like to tackle your question a little
bit later in the Q&A section. Is that okay?
Sure. Okay so as I
was saying we have an
exciting campaign
planned for the X420. Firstly
we'll have a nationwide
television campaign as well as
advertising on radio and also
in many computer publications.
We also intend to. I'm
sorry to stop you Mr.
Ford but do you really think
that a television campaign
is cost effective? I mean how
much is that going to cost?
Well I don't have the figures to
hand but I'd be happy to discuss those
figures with you
after the presentation.
Okay let me just go on
and talk a little more about
the exciting campaign
we have in store.
Alright so this was part
five of our presentation
series where halfway
done with it and so far
we've seen a lot of
interesting things and
as you notice it's an intermediate lesson
so it is a little bit more challenging and
a little bit longer than
your previous lessons.
That's right these are longer and some
of the phrases that you've learned, these
words are very difficult
but as a reminder some
of the words repeat.
So for example in today's
dialogue we heard a lot about developing
markets and campaigns but we also heard
about these last week
in episode four so you
know if you're confused
or you want some
extra practice I would
recommend listening to
some of the older
lessons again just to review
because you're going to hear a lot of these
words and phrases over and over again.
That's right and of course
if you have any questions
about this or any
suggestions you can also
come to our website
www.EnglishPod.com where
we'll see everyone there. That's right
so until next week bye everyone. Bye.